mcomet.com 2008-09-26

# privacy-policy

Mcomet and its affiliate sites are committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our Sites and Services. As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to inform visitors to the Sites and users of the Services how we use and protect the information we collect.

## Information Collected by Mcomet

When you register to become a member of Mcomet, you submit personally identifiable information such as your name and email address. As part of your personal profile, you may choose to submit additional information such as age, gender, location, interests and other content, such as photos.

We also collect other non-personally identifiable data, which may include your IP address and what browser you are using.

## Use of Information

We will display your personal information on your profile and elsewhere on the site according to the preferences you set in your account where it may be seen by other members or non-members. As with any online service, we encourage users to think carefully about what personal information they will disclose on their profile. 

We may use your information such as your age, zip code or IP address, to statistically analyze site usage and to customize our site's content, layout and services. The resulting information will allow us to improve our site and better understand and serve our users. 

We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our sites. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Unless you visit the Web site of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people when: 

### Personally identifiable information

  * 1\. You volunteer information or create a public profile in the course of your participation in our community features such as user opinions and reviews. 
  * 2\. When required by law, such as when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process. 
  * 3\. We believe that your actions violate applicable laws, Mcomet Terms of Use, or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others. 

### Aggregate information

We aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

## Reviewing and Changing Your Profile

You can review and revise your personal profile at any time. 

## Email Policies

We provide the service of inviting friends to see movies by sending emails to your friends. You have full control regarding whether you want to send emails to your friends or not. 

## Children

Children under the age of thirteen (13) are not eligible to use our service. If we become aware that any user is under the age of 13, we cancel their account and delete all of their personal information.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so.

## Acquisition or Business Transfer

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a merger, acquisition or reorganization of ownership of Mcomet. It is possible that an acquiring company may materially change this privacy policy.

## Security

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. Mcomet uses industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us.

## Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. Your continued usage of Mcomet constitutes an acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms of Service so we encourage you to visit this page periodically to review any changes. 

## Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us.
